Guide to the Louise Crane and Victoria Kent Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Louise Crane Papers, 1809-1998; Series I; 12.42; (13 boxes)
  - Financial Papers
    - First Agricultural Bank #1-1222, 1980-81 (Box 13)
    - First Agricultural Bank #1-1-1223, 1980-81 (Box 13)
    - First Agricultural Bank #1-1225, 1979-81 (Box 13)
    - Trust 1-312 income, 1975 (Box 13)
    - Account No. I-312 income, 1971-73 (Box 13)
    - A.G. Bank: Correspondence, 1978 (Box 13)
    - First Agricultural Bank #1-312, 1980-81 (Box 13)
    - Account No 1-312 principle, 1970-79 (Box 13)
    - Account No. 1-312 income, 1969-70 (Box 13)
    - Elaine Schaefer, 1966-79 (Box 13)
    - Kappo Brooks, 1977 (Box 13)
    - Ellen Bruzelius, 1978-79 (Box 13)
    - Tax Lamothe House-Profit/Loss & Investment Credit, 1974 (Box 13)
    - Department of State, 1973-82 (Box 13)
    - Lamothe House, New Orleans, 1974-75 (Box 13)
    - Lamothe House, New Orleans, occupancy records, 1978 (Box 13)
    - First Agricultural Bank Trust Division, 1977, 1987 (Box 13)
    - Will of Winthrop Murray Crane, undated (Box 13)
    - The Bank of New York, 1973-87 (Box 13)
    - Josephine Boardman Crane (Box 13)
    - The Bank of New York, statement and checks, 1973-87 (Box 13)
    - Appeals, 1986 (Box 13)
    - The Bank of New York, statements and checks, 1973-86 (Box 13)
    - Roger [Louise Crane's dog], 1964 (Box 13)
    - The Last Will and Testament of Josephine Boardman Crane, 1959, 1962 (Box 13)
    - Carl Cobb, 1980-82 (Box 13)
    - Crane and Company, 1980-86 (Box 13)
    - Mrs. Florence Keep, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Crane, Josephine Boardman, miscellaneous writings, 1931-60 (Box 13)
    - List of jewelry put in Bank of New York deposit box by Louise Crane, 1983 (Box 13)
    - Yale University, 1946 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence to and from libraries and readers, 1971-77 (Box 13)
    - Copyright: proof sheets; printing and binding bills, 1971 (Box 13)
    - Women's National Republican Club, 1970-71 (Box 13)
    - Josephine Boardman Crane, financial records relating to artwork, 1972-79 (Box 13)
    - Bank statements, miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 13)
- Harpsichord Music Society, 1957-1992; Series II; 6.04; (8 boxes)
  Correspondence, notes, financial papers, and printed material relating to the Harpsichord Music Society.
  - Taxes, 1977-86; 9 (Box 14)
  - Board information, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Bank-books/card miscellaneous, 1962-91 (Box 14)
  - Miss Ward, 1971-72 (Box 14)
  - Unemployment insurance, 1972-79 (Box 14)
  - Bank statements-1, 1972-81 (Box 14)
  - Bank statements-2, 1982-92 (Box 14)
  - Brinn, Lawrence, 1983-89 (Box 14)
  - Carnegie & Contracts, 1972-76 (Box 14)
  - Clark Dodge & Co., 1972-74 (Box 14)
  - Contributions, 1972-92 (Box 14)
  - Commissions, 1971-82 (Box 14)
  - Cooper, Kenneth, 1983-92 (Box 14)
  - Correspondence, 1972-92 (Box 14)
  - Fiduciary Trust Co. -(shields), 1975 (Box 14)
  - Garland Publishing, 1988-90 (Box 14)
  - Fenkel and Co., Inc., 1971-74 (Box 14)
  - Grants and scholarships, 1974-92 (Box 14)
  - Outline of the Harpsichord Music Society, undated (Box 14)
  - Kidder Peabody (see Clark Dodge), 1974-75 (Box 14)
  - LeShaw, Howard, 1972-92 (Box 14)
  - LeShaw, Howard-IRS copies, 1979-81 (Box 14)
  - Mackey, William, 1991-92 (Box 14)
  - Mannes College-Miscellaneous Inf., 1983-87 (Box 14)
  - Marlowe, Sylvia - A Tribute to - Concert, Dec. 10, 1985 (Box 14)
  - Marlowe, Sylvia - plus press & biography, 1972-76 (Box 14)
  - MCA Records, 1972-74 (Box 14)
  - Matthews, Shirley, 1990 (Box 14)
  - McDonnell Douglas, 1963-77 (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous records, 1988-89 (Box 15)
  - Paid bills, 1972-91 (Box 15)
  - Publicity concerts, etc., 1974-82 (Box 15)
  - Serenus contract, 1975 (Box 15)
  - Stroud, W. B. D., 1990 (Box 15)
  - Taxes, 1969-91; 11 (Box 15)
  - Correspondence, 1985-91; 4 (Box 15)
  - Correspondence, 1985-91; 4 (Box 16)
  - Go, magazine, 1941 (Box 16)
  - Photograph: Bruce Caulin, 1958 (Box 16)
  - Book 1: financial records March 1972 - June 1988, 1972-88 (Box 17)
  - Book 2: financial records June 1988 - April 1991, 1988-91 (Box 17)
  - Record of income February 1972- April 1991, 1972-91 (Box 17)
  - List of contributors, 1973-92 (Box 17)
  - Chemical Bank account statements, 1972-92; 9 (Box 17)
  - Chemical Bank account statements, 1972-92; 3 (Box 17)
  - Addresses, undated. (Box 17)
  - The Harpsichord Music Society, Inc. Minutes; Volume 1 April 1972-June 1984, 1972-84 (Box 18)
  - The Harpsichord Music Society, Inc. Minutes; Volume 2 Dec. 20 1984 - May 12, 1992, 1984-92 (Box 18)
  - Check book, 1972-77 (Box 18)
  - Check book, 1980-92 (Box 18)
  - Harpsichord Society official seal in wooden box, undated (Box 18)
  - Notebook, undated (Box 19)
  - Notebook (1), undated (Box 19)
  - Check book 10/14/57-12/16/63, 1957-63 (Box 19)
  - Howard Le Shaw tax information used 1971-1973
    - Tax Internal Revenue Service, 1959-69 (Box 19)
    - State of New York - Department of Law Attorney General Lekowitz, 1964-70 (Box 19)
    - Stock transactions, 1969 (Box 19)
    - Taxes, 1968 (Box 19)
  - Old Information, contracts from Sylvia Marlowe's book
    - Decca Contracts Harpsichord Music Society, 1964-66 (Box 19)
    - Ledger, 1957-72 (Box 19)
    - Certificate of Incorporation of The Harpsichord Music Society; photocopy of 1957 original, undated (Box 19)
    - Clark, Dodge,and Co., 1968 (Box 19)
    - Insurance policy, 1968 (Box 19)
  - Chemical Bank
    - Business reply envelopes for deposits, undated (Box 19)
    - Envelopes to hold statements, undated (Box 19)
    - Savings account withdrawal slips, undated (Box 19)
    - Correspondence; overdrawn notice, 1969 (Box 19)
    - Deposit slips, undated; 4 (Box 19)
  - Chemical Bank account statements, 1957-61; 5 (Box 19)
  - Chemical Bank account statements, 1962-69; 8 (Box 20)
  - Artist charcoal paper, undated (Box 20)
    Old material received from Miss Matier and Miss Ward ("after the death of Miss Matier, Miss Ward sorted all her old records and gave me the material in 1972")
  - Agreement and payments made to artist appearing in concerts, 1958-60 (Box 21)
  - Appeals for contributions to Harpsichord Music Society, 1959 (Box 21)
  - Board of Directors Harpsichord Music Society, 1957-60 (Box 21)
  - Carnegie Recital Hall, 1957-71 (Box 21)
  - Certificate of incorporation of Harpsichord Music Society, 1958-59 (Box 21)
  - Chemical Bank - power of attorney, etc., 1957-71 (Box 21)
  - Commissions - Harpsichord Music Society, 1957-64 (Box 21)
  - Contributions received for Harpsichord Music Society, 1957-71 (Box 21)
  - Cosmetto Artist Management, Inc. Mildred Shagal, Inc., 1962-64 (Box 21)
  - Cosmetto Data-Harpsichord Music Society, 1958-61 (Box 21)
  - Insurance - Harpsichord Music Society, 1962-69 (Box 21)
  - Inquiries - Harpsichord Music Society, 1957 (Box 21)
  - Memos, 1971-72 (Box 21)
  - Minutes of Harpsichord Music Society meeting April 18, 1957 and excerpts of April 30, 1963, 1957-71 (Box 21)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1959 (Box 21)
  - Nature of activities, undated (Box 21)
  - Notice of meetings, 1958 (Box 21)
  - Orders for the Harpsichord Music Society, 1971 (Box 21)
  - Paid bills, 1958-72 (Box 21)
  - Paid bills, 1957-62 (Box 21)
  - Recordings: Decca Records agreements, MCA etc., 1968-70 (Box 21)
  - Decca Records agreement, 1964-69 (Box 21)
  - MCA Records, 1970-71 (Box 21)
  - Sylvia Marlowe Harpsichord Scholarship -Cleveland Institute of Music, 1969-70 (Box 21)
  - Ticket sales, 1958-59 (Box 21)
  - Town Hall contracts, 1959-61 (Box 21)
  - Financial reports, investments
    - Harpsichord Music Society financial reports, 1957-62 (Box 21)
    - Harpsichord Music Society financial reports, 1969-71 (Box 21)
    - Harpsichord Music Society financial reports, 1963-68 (Box 21)
    - Investments, 1967-71 (Box 21)
  - Vittorio Rieti, Triptych, 1982-1983
- Victoria Kent Papers, 1936-1988; Series III; 12; (15 boxes)
  Correspondence, writings, notes, printed material, photographs, and personal papers relating to Victoria Kent.
  - Libreria del Colegio (Argentina), 1965-75 (Box 22)
  - Libreria del Colegio, 1958-63 (Box 22)
  - Libreria del Colegio, 1959-64 (Box 22)
  - Analecta Cisterciesia, 1979 (Box 22)
  - Copper plates with Victoria Kent's name on them, 1947 (Box 22)
  - Bibliográfia Perritereraria, 1948 (Box 22)
  - Cuatro Años en Paris (criticas), 1947 (Box 22)
  - Crónicas Radiadas, 1952-57 (Box 22)
  - Presentación de la Liga Internacional de los Derechos del Hombre, 1959 (Box 22)
  - Photocopies of photograph of Victoria Kent, undated (Box 22)
  - Various photographs and drawings, undated (Box 22)
  - Adams, Mildred, 1959-77 (Box 23)
  - Andreu Abello-José Barcelona, 1970-72 (Box 23)
  - Advisory Board, 1967-75 (Box 23)
  - Alba, Victor, 1954-60 (Box 23)
  - Alcala-Zamora, Niceto, 1955-75 (Box 23)
  - Arana, José-Domingo de, 1967-68 (Box 23)
  - Alvarez De Toledo-Isabel Duquesa de Median Sidonia, 1972-74 (Box 23)
  - Saurez-Macrino Francia, 1972-75 (Box 23)
  - Arde, 1971-84 (Box 23)
  - Accion R. Democrática, 1959-74 (Box 23)
  - Ayensa-Alfonso Mexico, 1954-75 (Box 23)
  - Azana, 1979-85 (Box 23)
  - Listas (Propoganda y posibles suscriptores), 1959-61 (Box 23)
  - Azcarte, Justino de Caracas, Venezuela, 1956-73 (Box 23)
  - Ballester-Gozalvo-José Francia, 1969 (Box 23)
  - Bartres, 1958-70 (Box 23)
  - Bowers, H.E. Mr. Claude, 1954-58 (Box 23)
  - Beitia-Pedro de; Washington, D.C., 1967-73 (Box 23)
  - Beltran De Heredia-Pablo, 1966-69 (Box 23)
  - Romulo Betancourt, 1956-57 (Box 23)
  - Bordonabo, Emilio, 1962-75 (Box 23)
  - Botella, Virgilio, 1954-75 (Box 23)
  - Bellejos-José; Mexico, D.F., 1969-73 (Box 23)
  - Camus, Albert, 1953-60 (Box 23)
  - Carpio-Campio (Argentina), 1974 (Box 23)
  - Carretero Y Jimenez-Anselmo; Mexico, 1954-68 (Box 23)
  - Cartas a los Presidentes de los Estados Unidos, 1960 (Box 23)
  - Casals, Pablo, 1953-74 (Box 23)
  - Civil Liberties Union of California, 1957-58 (Box 23)
  - Comision de Homenaje a Victoria Ocampo, 1962 (Box 23)
  - Comité Nacional De Ayuda A Espana, 1938-39 (Box 23)
  - Comité Popular de Ayuda los Refugiados Espanoles, 1938-39 (Box 23)
  - Iberica Council, 1961-70 (Box 23)
  - Congreso de los Diputados, 1937-39 (Box 23)
  - Consejo Federal Español del Movimiento Europeo, 1958 (Box 23)
  - Consuelo Berges, 1978-80 (Box 23)
  - Dirigida Por Victoria Ocampo, 1946-48 (Box 23)
  - Curriculum Vitae, undated (Box 23)
  - Garcia Cova, Luis, 1949-78 (Box 23)
  - Darnaude Igacio, D., 1957-58 (Box 23)
  - del Rio, Angel 600 West 116 St. N.Y., 1956-62 (Box 23)
  - Dethorey, Ernesto, 1959-70 (Box 23)
  - Daiz-Marta, Manuel, 1966-84 (Box 23)
  - Diez, Antonia, 1958-67 (Box 23)
  - Ebenstein, William, 1959-70 (Box 23)
  - Elosegui, Alberto, 1972-75 (Box 24)
  - Emílio, Juan, 1966-67 (Box 24)
  - España, 1954-70 (Box 24)
  - Espontaneos, 1954-74 (Box 24)
  - Estrugo, José M. Cuba, 1956-58 (Box 24)
  - L'Express, 1959-61 (Box 24)
  - Fitelson, William, 1953-56 (Box 24)
  - Flores, 1959-61 (Box 24)
  - Flores-Xavier, 1960-61 (Box 24)
  - Francia: correspondence, 1956-59 (Box 24)
  - Foix, Pere, 1957-63 (Box 24)
  - Victoria Kent-Declaration, 1978 (Box 24)
  - Garces Arroyo, Santiago (A.D.I) Mexico, 1957-60 (Box 24)
  - Garcia Duran, Juan Huston, Texas, 1965-69 (Box 24)
  - Garcia Valdes, Carlos, Director de Instituciones Penitenciarias Madrid, 1978-1980 (Box 24)
  - Garcitotal, Allicio, 1957-75 (Box 24)
  - Garcia, Manuel (Alemania), 1960-1961 (Box 24)
  - Garcia Polanco-Bernabé, 1963-64 (Box 24)
  - Garrio, Primitivo Uruguay, 1955-58 (Box 24)
  - Gil Robles, Jose Ma., 1962-65 (Box 24)
  - Ariadna, undated; 9 (Box 25)
  - Dedicatoria, undated (Box 25)
  - El Vortice, undated (Box 25)
  - Una República Para España Portigo y Semaforo Capítulo 1 José Mariá Semprum Gurrea, 1936-38 (Box 25)
  - Capitulo Segundo, undated (Box 25)
  - Una Republica Para España Capitulo 3, undated (Box 25)
  - Una Republica Para España Capitulo IV, undated (Box 25)
  - Primera y Segunda Parte Jose Marriade, undated (Box 25)
  - Semprun Gurrea, undated (Box 25)
  - Monodialogos No. 1, undated (Box 25)
  - Monodialogos No. 2, undated (Box 25)
  - Monodialogos Int.-V, undated; 2 (Box 25)
  - Monodialogos Chapter VII-XII, undated (Box 25)
  - Pórtico Y semaforo, undated (Box 25)
  - Espagna, Rusia Y El Este, 1966-70 (Box 26)
  - Feduchi, Sr. D. Manuel Martinez, 1955-1965 (Box 26)
  - Latin American Conference, 1950-51 (Box 26)
  - Mackay, Dr. John, 1953-69 (Box 26)
  - Madariaga, 1953-56 (Box 26)
  - Mendizabal, Alfredo, 1962-69 (Box 26)
  - Mexico and Cuba, 1954-56 (Box 26)
  - Miscellaneous, 1953-63; 6 (Box 26)
  - Morodo, Raul, 1963-68 (Box 26)
  - Movimiento Espagnol, 1959-73 (Box 26)
  - Muñoz Suay, Sr. D. Ricardo, 1956-57 (Box 26)
  - New York Times, 1953-56 (Box 26)
  - University of Nevada, Reno, 1972-75 (Box 26)
  - Ortega, Soledad, 1980 (Box 26)
  - Otero, Mariano, 1970-74 (Box 26)
  - Palma, 1962 (Box 26)
  - Paret, Maria Victoria, 1955-1960 (Box 26)
  - Partridge, Frances, 1959-61 (Box 26)
  - Pego, Sr. D. Aurelio, 1967-75 (Box 26)
  - Peirat, Mr. Julian, 1969-71 (Box 26)
  - Perez, Minik-Domingo, 1947-68 (Box 26)
  - Picasso, 1972-81 (Box 26)
  - Pingarron, Angel, 1960-67 (Box 26)
  - Pinzon Jimenez, Francisco H., 1957-85 (Box 26)
  - Pons-Prades, M. Eduardo, 1958-63 (Box 26)
  - Pons Prades, eduardo, 1973-76 (Box 26)
  - Porter, Rep. Chales O., 1957-60 (Box 26)
  - Post N.Y., 1954-62 (Box 26)
  - Prado Rodriguez, 1956-75 (Box 26)
  - Prieto, Indalecio, 1954-63 (Box 26)
  - Prisoner, 1969-80 (Box 26)
  - Prisoners, 1977-81 (Box 26)
  - Protest Ridruejo, 1964 (Box 26)
  - Protest April 15, 1954 (Box 26)
  - Purmany, Antoni, 1956-58 (Box 26)
  - Ramos d'Acosta, 1967-73 (Box 26)
  - Ruether, Victor, 1953-61 (Box 26)
  - Rincon, Luciano, 1959-74 (Box 26)
  - Rivas Cherif, Cipriano, 1954-55 (Box 26)
  - Roberts, William H. Vanderbilt University, 1958-61 (Box 26)
  - Rodriguez-Olleros, Dr. Angel, 1970-74 (Box 26)
  - Ruíz-Gimenez, Joaquín, 1969 (Box 26)
  - Ruedo Ibérico-Editions, 1964-75 (Box 26)
  - Sagrera, Martin, 1967-72 (Box 27)
  - Sanchez-Mazas,Miguel, 1957-74 (Box 27)
  - Sanz, Jose, 1961-66 (Box 27)
  - Saori, Mercedes, 1983-84 (Box 27)
  - Sardoya, 1972-81 (Box 27)
  - Sauer and Auvermann, 1972-75 (Box 27)
  - Semprun Gurrea, Jose Ma. de, 1954-58 (Box 27)
  - Semprun Gurrea, Jose Ma de, 1959-63 (Box 27)
  - Semprun Gurrea, Jose Ma de, 1967-72 (Box 27)
  - Senate correspondence, 1953-62 (Box 27)
  - Sindicato de Prensa Latino Americano, 1959 (Box 27)
  - Solari, Juan Antonio, 1963-65 (Box 27)
  - Subira, Sr. D. Angel, 1962-69 (Box 27)
  - Alexander, Robert J., 1953-63 (Box 28)
  - Arauz, Dr. Eugenio, 1969 (Box 28)
  - Argentina (Cuentas Carranza), 1954-64 (Box 28)
  - Viaje A La Agentina De Victoria, 1964, 1984 (Box 28)
  - Ateneo Demalaga, 1980-81 (Box 28)
  - Banco Urquijo, 1979-81 (Box 28)
  - Bank of New York, 1964-74 (Box 28)
  - Barcelona, 1960-64 (Box 28)
  - Berle, Rudolf, 1953-61 (Box 28)
  - Biblbao, Pedro, 1957-75 (Box 28)
  - Bort-Vela, J., 1955-75 (Box 28)
  - Carranza, Carlos, 1959-65 (Box 28)
  - Carranza, Sr. Carlos P., 1954-59 (Box 28)
  - Christian Science Monitor, 1954-55 (Box 28)
  - Consaile Berges, undated (Box 28)
  - Coto De Donana, 1972-73 (Box 28)
  - Cranks, 1954-62 (Box 28)
  - Cuatrocasas, Juan, 1957-62 (Box 28)
  - Delgado, 1954-65 (Box 28)
  - Diaz-Marta, 1975-79 (Box 28)
  - Editorial Bruguera y Consuelo Berges, 1954-81 (Box 28)
  - Escuela de Capacitacion, 1948-51 (Box 28)
  - Elbaile, Javier, 1958-66 (Box 28)
  - Etcheverria, Salvador, 1953-57 (Box 28)
  - Ferninisno, Sobre, 1977 (Box 28)
  - Flanner, Carmen, 1952-69 (Box 28)
  - Flores, Javier, 1961-69 (Box 28)
  - Flores, Xavier, 1961-69 (Box 28)
  - Galvao, Henrique, 1962-64 (Box 28)
  - Giddons, Rev. Father William, 1948-61 (Box 28)
  - Giner de los Rios, Bernardo, 1953-70 (Box 28)
  - Gobierno Republicano, 1952 (Box 28)
  - Hallman Hamilton, 1961-63 (Box 28)
  - Hicke, Miss Dorothy, 1954-56 (Box 28)
  - Ibérica, 1953-59 (Box 28)
  - Ibérica, 1953-74 (Box 28)
  - Ibérica miscellaneous, 1968-69 (Box 28)
  - Iglesias, Ignacio, 1954-73 (Box 28)
  - The International League for the Rights of Man, 1957-66 (Box 28)
  - International Commission for Jurist, 1949-83 (Box 29)
  - International Confederation for Free Trade Unions, 1957-60 (Box 29)
  - Jimenez de Asua, Don Luis, 1950-63 (Box 29)
  - Kent, Victoria #1, 1961-75 (Box 29)
  - Kent, Victoria #2, 1958-78 (Box 29)
  - Kent, Victoria; articles, 1936-82 (Box 29)
  - Kent, Victoria; miscellaneous, 1958-86 (Box 29)
  - Kerrigan, Anthony, 1961-71 (Box 29)
  - League for Labor Research, 1959 (Box 29)
  - Lea Navas, Jesus, 1957-61 (Box 29)
  - Limosner, Sr. D. Enrique, 1954-57 (Box 29)
  - Llach, Guillermina, 1950-52 (Box 29)
  - Lopez Alvarez, Luis, 1956 (Box 29)
  - Lopez Aparicio, Sr. V., 1961-62 (Box 29)
  - Primo de Rivera, 1946-66 (Box 29)
  - Unidentified, 1954-63 (Box 29)
  - Eduardo Ortega Y Gasset, 1956 (Box 30)
    Victoria: Estos son sus editoriales. Faltan dos fotocopias (es decir, hay que sacarlas). Ya le explicará. Lo importante es que ya están todos reunidos (español).
  - Etchevarria, Salvador, 1953-54 (Box 30)
  - Inventario de libros propiedad de Louise Crane
    - Madariaja, 1959-75; 2 (Box 30)
    - Encuentro Con Victoria Kent, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Sender, Ranion, 1953-59 (Box 30)
    - Arbeloa, Victor Manuel, 1968 (Box 30)
  - Ninos entregados a sus familias, 1937-39 (Box 30)
  - Morodo, Raul Marques de Cubas 6 Madrid 14, 1969-73 (Box 30)
  - Otero Seco, Antonio, 1957-70 (Box 30)
  - Photographs; Ibérica, 1962-63 (Box 30)
  - Primera Parte, Fundamentos Ideologicos de Accion Republicana Democratica Espanola Arde, 1979 (Box 30)
  - Queroga, 1939-45 (Box 30)
  - Ridruejo, Dionisio, 1962-68 (Box 30)
  - Tierno, Emrique, 1966-74 (Box 30)
  - United Nations, 1949-52; 2 (Box 30)
  - Miscellaneous, undated; 3 (Box 30)
  - Giral, Francisco, 1968-74 (Box 31)
  - Girbau, Vicente, 1958-59 (Box 31)
  - Gironella, Enrique, 1957-60 (Box 31)
  - Gobierno Republicano, 1960-66 (Box 31)
  - Gonzalez Lopez, Emilio, 1968 (Box 31)
  - Gordon Ordas, Felix, 1953-73; 2 (Box 31)
  - Gorkin, Julian, 1963-72; 2 (Box 31)
  - Goytisolo, Juan, 1963 (Box 31)
  - Granados, Mariano, 1963 (Box 31)
  - Garcia-Mariano, 1960 (Box 31)
  - Grant, Frances, 1952-60 (Box 31)
  - Griffiss, James E., 1969 (Box 31)
  - Gullien, Claudio, 1965 (Box 31)
  - Guillen, Jorge, 1965 (Box 31)
  - Haya de la Torre, V.R., 1955-56 (Box 31)
  - Historia 16, 1956-78 (Box 31)
  - Mathews, Herbert, 1956-61 (Box 31)
  - Herter, 1957 (Box 31)
  - Huerrta, Jose Felix, 1965-68 (Box 31)
  - Hurtado, Victor, 1964-68 (Box 31)
  - India News, 1954-56 (Box 31)
  - Infante, Isidro, 1966-68 (Box 31)
  - Irujo, Manuel De, 1964-74; 2 (Box 31)
  - America Magazine, 1958 (Box 31)
  - Just, Julio, 1953-72; 2 (Box 31)
  - Lemoneda Izquierdo, Ramón, 1954-55 (Box 31)
  - Liarte Ramón, 1957-60 (Box 31)
  - Listas, 1960 (Box 31)
  - Lopez, Carlos, 1969 (Box 31)
  - Argentina (Lorenzo), 1967-72 (Box 31)
  - Ligue Des Mutiles, 1956-74 (Box 31)
  - Luis, Leopoldo de, 1961 (Box 31)
  - Maldonado, Jose, 1972-74; 2 (Box 31)
  - Madariaga, 1957 (Box 31)
  - Madariaga, 1958 (Box 31)
  - Marichal, Juan, 1961-71 (Box 31)
  - Llopis, Rodolfo, 1955-74 (Box 31)
  - Luna, Pedro, 1963-65 (Box 31)
  - Marcos Estrada, Manuel, 1958-60 (Box 31)
  - Marquez, Antonio, 1956-58 (Box 31)
  - Martin, Rafaél, 1956-58 (Box 31)
  - Martinez Barrio Diego, 1952-56 (Box 31)
  - Martinez, Saura-Santos, 1966-74 (Box 31)
  - Miscellaneous, 1954-78 (Box 31)
  - Madariaga, 1963-72 (Box 32)
  - Martinez, Antonio, 1966-76 (Box 32)
  - Madariaga, Emilia de, 1960-80 (Box 32)
  - Miscellaneous, 1950-70; 17 (Box 32)
  - Moiron, Sara, 1972-75 (Box 32)
  - Molins Fabrega, Narciso, 1957 (Box 32)
  - Montero, Isaac; Montero, Julian, 1966-67 (Box 32)
  - Rosa Montera, 1979 (Box 32)
  - Montesinos, Manuel, 1964-65 (Box 32)
  - Montezuma, Joaquim, 1960-76 (Box 32)
  - Morera, 1958-59 (Box 32)
  - Navarro, Tomas, 1954 (Box 32)
  - Morrison, Ray, 1961 (Box 32)
  - Navarro, Ernesto, 1954-65 (Box 32)
  - Nogueras, Samuell, 1954-69 (Box 32)
  - Novias, Jose, 1963-69 (Box 32)
  - O'Kean, 1979-85 (Box 32)
  - Onís, Frederico de, 1954 (Box 32)
  - Opus Dei, 1950-60 (Box 32)
  - Oliver Bertrand, Rafael, 1965-66 (Box 32)
  - Portugal Commission for Democracy, 1962-72 (Box 32)
  - Oram, Harold, 1954 (Box 32)
  - Orive, Mario de, 1958-64 (Box 32)
  - Ortega, Jose, 1974 (Box 32)
  - Ortega y Gasset, Eduardo, 1956-58 (Box 32)
  - Otero Seco, Antonio, 1959-61; 2 (Box 32)
  - Spanish Institute, 1955-56 (Box 33)
  - Committee for a Democratic Spain, 1952-1967 (Box 33)
  - Sadler, George, 1953-56 (Box 33)
  - Stuber, Stanley, 1954-55 (Box 33)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1959-64 (Box 33)
  - Tribune Des Nátións, 1963-66 (Box 33)
  - Association of Evangelicals, 1954-56 (Box 33)
  - UNESCO protest, 1993 (Box 33)
  - Various letters, 1960-62 (Box 33)
  - Wolf, Jules, 1963-64 (Box 33)
  - Western Union, 1970-89 (Box 33)
  - Portugal, 1966-69 (Box 33)
  - Soares, Mario, 1960-70; 2 (Box 33)
  - Sociedades Hispañas Confederades, 1953-61 (Box 33)
  - Spanish Refugee Aid, 1950-70; 2 (Box 33)
  - Spanish Refugee Aid Committee, 1950-70 (Box 33)
  - Sanchez-Albornoz, Claudio, 1956-62 (Box 33)
  - Sender, Ramon, 1956-74 (Box 33)
  - Serra Y Morat, Manuel, 1954-57 (Box 33)
  - Sherman, Arnold, 1956 (Box 33)
  - Telegram to Eisenhauer, 1959 (Box 33)
  - Tierno Galvan, Enrique, 1960-66 (Box 33)
  - Tomás, Jaime, 1980 (Box 33)
  - Tomás, Pascual, 1950-60 (Box 33)
  - Torres, Aldo, 1960 (Box 33)
  - Torres Gallego, Emilio, 1980 (Box 33)
  - Torres Campan, Don, 1958-67 (Box 33)
  - Tovar, Antonio, 1968-75 (Box 33)
  - Tunan de la Lara, Manuel, 1968-76 (Box 33)
  - Unamuno, Maria, 1957-64 (Box 33)
  - United Nations, 1952; 2 (Box 33)
  - Valencia, 1961-66 (Box 33)
  - Valera, Fernando, 1956-72; 2 (Box 33)
  - Vascos, 1965-66 (Box 33)
  - Vidal y Planas, Alfonso, 1963-65 (Box 33)
  - Vilar, Sergio, 1967-69 (Box 33)
  - Viguri, Ramón, 1958 (Box 33)
  - Victoria Secretária en Paris, 1939 (Box 33)
  - Viladas, Ramón, 1959 (Box 33)
  - Vila Selma, Enrique, 1969 (Box 33)
  - Villar, Manuel del, 1958-73 (Box 33)
  - Washington Post, 1958-65 (Box 33)
  - Whitaker, Arthur, 1961 (Box 33)
  - Ibérica [bound copies], 1953-74; 7 (Box 34)
  - Index folders for Ibérica, undated; 2 (Box 34)
  - Metal box with file cards used as an address book, undated (Box 34)
  - Photographs from social events, production promos and galas
    - Readings and events, 1980 (Box 35)
    - Readings and luncheon, 1983 (Box 35)
    - Readings and events, 1981-82; 2 (Box 35)
    - Luncheon pictures from various years, undated (Box 35)
    - Building renovations, 1982 (Box 35)
    - Office activity 0-1 to 0-38, undated (Box 35)
    - Production observance P-1 to P-3, undated (Box 35)
    - Craft discussion C-1 to C-35, undated (Box 35)
    - Luncheon, 1967 (Box 35)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 35)
    - Composer-Librettist Studio, 1986 (Box 35)
    - Readings, 1982-86 (Box 35)
    - Members and Alumni various dates (Box 35)
    - Doodles auction, 1985-86 (Box 35)
    - Social S-1 to S-8, undated (Box 35)
    - Promotional photographs, 1986 (Box 35)
    - Stills from Madonna in the Orchard, 1968 (Box 35)
    - Production and readings, 1960-79 (Box 35)
    - Special events and readings, undated (Box 35)
    - Workshop W-24 to W-68, undated (Box 35)
    - New Dramatists, 1987-88 (Box 35)
    - Exchange program with various countries around the world, undated (Box 35)
  - Printed material, 1974-95; 8
- Oversize and Other Storage, 0.71; (3 boxes)
  - Oversize
    - Sketch pads (Series I), 1968; 1975, undated; 3 (Box 37 (Oversize))
    - Resolution (Series I), 1946 Mar 26 (Box 37 (Oversize))
    - Stephen Crane, portrait (Series I), undated (Box 37 (Oversize))
    - Mabel Boardman, portrait (Series I), undated (Box 37 (Oversize))
    - School children (Series I), undated (Box 37 (Oversize))